SRAVANI **MAITY**

WEB DEVELOPER



- 7709279628
- shravanimaity0011@gmail.com
- Remote or any city (Nagpur is native)
- My-Portfolio

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript / ES6
- React.Js
- Redux Tool Kit

TOOLS USED

- Vs Code (IDE)
- Git Desktop
- JIRA

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

St. Ursula Girl's High School [SSC]

2011-2012

JUNIOR COLLEGE

SFS Junior college [HSC]

2012-2014

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Laxminarayan Institute of tech, Nagpur

2014-2018

PROFILE

I have 1+ year of experience in Frontend development. I am passionate about learning New technologies and implementing them. I hold experience in Real time projects, developed website from scratch while working with small, agile team.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER Minutes to Seconds pvt ltd

Project-Name: RSTware [May 2022- July 2022]

RSTware was ongoing project, it was about dashboard and data distribution in homepage and also was about bluetooth pairing (APIs was given by client).

Team size - 2

- Developed UI withReact.js for small graphs used "npm i vector".
- Worked on login authentication with given API link by client.
- Fetched data from Json file.
- Used Redux tool kit to show data accordingly on reusable components.

Poject Name - TalentMiner(CRM Web App) [Aug 2021- May 2022]

Talentminer is an Australian job portal for australian candidate to search job and clients to post job of their respective Firm and admin to handle both candidate and client data.

Team size - 4

- Developed 30+ responsive UI pages with core HTML5 and CSS3 (JSX) in React.js.
- Worked on reusable components to make it more efficient.
- Routed multiple webpages accordingly using React-Router-Dom.
- For functionality, "Redux-tool-kit" to pass data across Application .

Poject Name - TeamBeforeSelf [May 2021- July 2021]

TeamBeforeSelf is a U.S military social media app, which is specifically for military person to get participated in various events which would be get posted in App.

Team size - 3

- Made UI webpages with React.js for App's Homepage, Friend Request, Event Page.
- Added form validation in profile setting page using React-Hook-Form library.
- Routed multiple webpages accordingly using React-Router-Dom.
- Added Calender for creating events in App using Calendar library.
- Worked on to Get an Axios request.